The weather is so nice today. Huh?
Everything's so peaceful.
Just look at those Goddess.
Not a monster in sight. Wait a sec.
Now is not the time to be daydreaming.
We've been traveling for eight hours.
There's just one question.
Where in the world are
these guys taking me?
I don't know.
I'll
The director contracted
us for a large-scale
project to reinforce the
village wall starting today.
So he asked us to take
you there so you could set
up shop on the construction
site to help us out.
Huh?
He said that?
Hold on.
Isn't that the guy who tried to steal
money from me during the expedition?
Maybe he turned over a new
leaf and got some honest work.
Well, if Director Bear hired
them, it should be fine.
Hello there!
That means yes, right? Excellent.
Wait just a moment, it will
get you where you need to go.
Be careful not to drop him. Yeah.
Okay, we're good to go. Got it.
Oh, man.
The more I think about
this whole situation,
I'm starting to realize I should have been
a little more suspicious of their story.
But still, how much
farther are we going to go?
Might as well double-check
my points to be safe.
I could use my barrier, but it
wouldn't even last for three hours.
Now I kind of regret going
that wild with my spending
after I earned a whole bunch
of points in the village.
Stop. We'll break here.
Man, I'm sore all over.
I'm going to go take a leak.
Yeah, me too.
Now's my chance.
I'll record these guys' faces
with my security camera.
Long time no see.
Remember me, Boxo?
He's a small-time crook.
I was a fool for thinking he reformed.
By now, I'm sure you
understand the whole situation.
So cooperate and spit
out some goodies or else.
You may not have a brain,
but even you should know what'll happen
if you don't do exactly as we say.
Too bad. What, fat?
You want to learn the hard way?
One damage.
Durability has been
decreased by one. Cut it out.
Though our main goal is the money inside,
the box itself should be worth something.
Don't lower its selling price.
Oh, you're right.
Sorry about that, boss. And you.
It'd be a real shame if you got busted up.
It'd be easier for everyone
if you did what you're told.
You had too bad.
I wanted to give you the option
to not get hurt, you know.
Hey, did I hear you right?
that it can fix any damage it takes
yep i watched it get pretty banged up
but now it's in perfect condition it's
definitely got a recovery skill all
right you can use force as long as you
don't break it you got it boss come
on let's get started boys like this
you're like giving up you stupid boss
durability has been decreased by three
all in all these guys aren't doing
that much damage to me but I hate the
fact I have to sit here and just take
it too would you like to spend 1,000
points to increase your toughness
by 10 what I can use points to enhance
my stats that's new did it get harder
damage taken zero great
no more damage for me okay
that's probably enough
for now uh yes sir hey you
said it fix itself huh no
way i swear i saw it do
it come on repair yourself
already goyle you know
what'll happen to you if
this thing is broken don't
you hey you wake up i know
you're just pretending
you can't fix see here
it's fine boss the hell
is this who knows let's
give Let's give it a try.
It tastes like shit!
Serves you right.
How do you like the taste of one of the
juices that ranks in my ten worst products?
Hurry up.
Bring it inside so our
guests can check it out.
But boss, what do we do if they
refuse to take a look at it?
If you can't get such a simple task
done, I swear your heads are gonna roll!
Count on us!
It sounds like there's someone else here.
The boss really doesn't let up, does he?
Yeah, you've said it.
Hey, we brought you something interesting,
so give it a once-over
and tell us what it is.
Huh?
Who the hell do you
think you're talking to?
Talk about an attitude.
You're a shitty little peon.
Sounds like a woman, too.
What makes you think
you can order me around?
Here's all the info we have on this thing.
Make sure you read through it.
Oh, yeah?
Where the hell are your manners?
Didn't your mother teach you to look people
in the eye when you're talking to them?
Wait, you seem like a mama's boy.
Could it be you're
scared of little old me?
Just figure it out!
The only thing you're any
good at is running away.
Tell me, are you really
a sentient magic item?
It might be too much of a
risk to tell her the truth.
Oh, sorry.
I should have introduced myself first.
The name's Hulemy.
Nice to meet you.
Huh?
I've heard that name before.
Anyway, I may not look it,
but I'm a magic item engineer.
Looks like the reason they kidnapped
me was so I could study you.
Oh!
She's the person Lamas wanted me to meet.
Hello there! Whoa!
You can really talk?
I've never seen a magic item that can
comprehend human speech before. Hello there!
Let's see.
It says here that
particular phrase means yes.
What a strange twist of fate
for us to run into each other.
I've actually experimented with trying to
endow magic items with human intelligence.
But in the end, I've concluded
it's currently impossible.
So then I changed up
the way I approached it.
Instead of giving a magic
item human intelligence,
I thought that I'd try
to put a human soul?
inside a magic item, see?
Whoa, she came up with
that idea all on her own?
Sorry, I don't usually get that worked up.
I'll get something to cool off.
Is this drink for me?
Hello there!
I'll help myself then.
Huh?
How do you open this thing?
Oh, I see.
It's so good!
This is so refreshing!
It's the perfect pick-me-up!
I don't know how you did it,
but it's pleasantly warm.
Thank you, really.
She's got a totally different
vibe when she smiles.
She's like a regular innocent girl.
I see.
So your name is Boxo. Hello there.
You're clearly sentient.
Are you a magic item that's had
a human soul placed inside it?
Hello there.
That's what I thought.
Since you can only respond yes
or no, I'll do the talking,
and you tell me if I've got it right.
Hello there.
You're a magic item, so do you
have a master somewhere? Too bad.
Ah, free agent, huh?
Do you have any memories
from when you were human?
Hello there.
Ooh, that's interesting.
Next question.
Normally, magic items aren't
supposed to require money to work.
The fact that you charge
makes you even more special.
Could it be you need money to replenish
your inventory? Hello there. Too bad.
Not wrong, but not
completely correct either.
Let's see.
Does that mean you have some
other use for the money you earn?
Hello there! Hello there!
It might be quicker to
just show her what I mean.
So bright!
What the hell did you do, Boxxo?
And it looks like the goods
you're selling are different too!
Whoa!
If I weren't a vending machine, this
would be a super awkward situation.
I see.
So that's what you use the money on.
You can somehow spend
it to change your form.
Hello there! How cool!
What other secrets you got
inside that metal frame?
What is this?
It's some kind of wall.
And I'd say a pretty sturdy one, too.
Now for a little surprise.
A solid wall where you can
control what passes through it?
This is a barrier, isn't it?
You're incredible!
Not only can you change your form,
but you can even use a blessing!
You are way beyond any
ordinary magic item.
While I appreciate the compliment,
all I did was die and get this
awesome vending machine body.
What's actually impressive
here is her intellect.
She's connecting all the dots and
pretty much figuring it out by herself.
I wonder if anybody back in the
village has noticed that I'm missing.
I hope Lamas doesn't get too worried
and end up doing something reckless.
Well?
Check it out.
Auxo's all fixed up now.
Shh.
Never mind the box.
Looks like she's asleep.
That smart-ass little girl.
Why don't we teach her a lesson?
You want to attack her while
she's totally defenseless?
You cowards.
I've got to stop this.
Hold on What's going on with the box?
Help!
I just remembered.
I have to do something back in my room.
My tummy hurts. I'll be back!
I'm kind of tired.
I'm good at taking that.
Oh, I'm glad it worked out, but I
really don't feel good about it.
Food time!
Then back to work!
Too bad!
Geez, what's with this thing?
If food's here, it must
be morning already.
Hey, Boxo!
Hello there!
Those jerks never give me anything good.
Sorry I can't trust them
not to slip something
weird into my food so I
haven't been eating much.
What's up?
Oh you changed your wares again.
Is this bread boy?
Am I glad to see this.
Oh, it's tasty.
How is it so soft and fluffy?
With food as good as this,
I bet you'd put all the
restaurants around out of business.
I ended up eating way
too much. I'm stuffed.
Huh?
What do you want?
Have you figured out
anything about this box yet?
I don't take orders from you.
You're not my boss.
A word of warning, I'm not a patient man.
You've got two days to find a way to open
up this box and get the money out of it.
You hear?
Guess we're on a time limit now.
We've got to make our escape before then.
Look at that.
Kulami's hair is a crazy mess.
But there's no bath here for her to use.
Hold on!
Is that another gift for me?
I really owe you a lot, Oxo.
Thanks to you, I can eat and drink.
Water?
But it's way warmer than usual.
Am I supposed to drink it?
Too bad you could use
your head did you say
head are you telling
me to use these things?
To wash my hair oh yeah
i haven't had a chance
to wash at all since those
jerks locked me up in
this place.
This is the kind of
situation I wanted to foster.
Reincarnation is the best.
Um,
I want to make sure it's
perfectly clear that
I bought women's underwear
purely by mistake.
It was an accident.
I feel like a new person.
Thanks, Voxo. Hello there.
Anyway, the deadline
Minus tomorrow morning.
What can we do?
Maybe I can create some kind of
distraction while Hulani runs away?
Otherwise...
Listen.
Do you mind if we talk about
something serious here?
Hello there!
Boxxo,
if you're thinking of trying to sacrifice
yourself so I can escape, just forget it.
There are hordes of monsters
that live in these parts.
I'm not a fighter, so I'd give myself
a few days at most before I got eaten.
Too bad!
That's why escaping from here
alone has never been an option.
We'll have to keep putting up
with this and wait for our chance.
And besides, at worst,
we'll die. Not a big deal.
Well, it might be for others, but I've
grown numb to that particular fear.
Is she for real?
I can't imagine what she's
experienced to feel that way.
It's getting late now.
I'm heading off to bed.
Good night.
I look forward to serving you again.
Holy crap.
She's got a real talent
for falling asleep.
What the hell was that?
This is our opportunity
to get out of here.
I've got to wake Hula me up
you could even win a reward
what time is it what's wrong
Voxo I don't know what's going
on out there whatever it is
it's good for us that voice
Lamas is here hold on that's Lamas's voice
did the hunters
association come to save us
and i think i heard her
calling out your name
wait a sec do the two
of you know each other
hello there what a small world if her group
is here everything should work out fine
let's stay put so we
don't get in their way
they can handle it hello
there all right then
hey boxo you've got my
back don't you hello there
you can count on me
don't worry i'll keep you
safe although we might
actually be in a bad spot
here too bad there's a
storehouse above us that's
where they're keeping all
the gold coins they've
stolen but that's not all
those idiots are hoarding
blastite too in other
words we've got a bomb
that can go off at any
moment just above our heads
that's so stupid
we're okay thanks to you i
knew i could count on you boxo
so uh i hope you can maintain
your barrier indefinitely
too bad dang once i run out
of points we'll get crushed
i can probably survive if i
buff my toughness but if i let
her die i'll never be able
to forgive myself i refuse to
give up and let that happen
there has to be some other way
hey boxo just checking you
need money in order to keep
your blessing going right hello
there look over there what
the gold do you see it that's our lifeline
all right i'll let it through the barrier
Great!
I can buy whatever I
want with all this money.
If we can hold out for three days, Llamas
and the others will probably reach us.
All we have to do is wait.
What happened?
She was fine a second ago.
My head is killing me.
Oh, I'm such an idiot.
She isn't getting enough oxygen.
The air's getting thinner because
we're sealed under the rubble.
What do I do?
Hulani's running out of time.
Got it!
What's that?
The sheep.
Is it supposed to go over my mouth?
Hello there!
Thank goodness I was a vending
machine fanatic in my previous life.
This oxygen vending machine
was introduced to the
general public in 1965 to
help combat air pollution.
Thank you, Oxo.
If you were a human being, I'm not sure
I could help myself falling for you.
Huh?
Vending machine or not?
Hearing you say that makes my
heart, I mean, my internals, pound.
Boxxo!
Where are you? Answer me! They found us!
Lamas is calling for you.
Don't make her wait. Hello there!
Boxxo!
I can hear your voice!
Homo there!
You're okay!
I'm so relieved!
25 damage.
Durability has been decreased by 25.
That hurt a bit more than I expected.
Sorry, it's my fault!
This happened because
I took my eyes off you!
Thank you very much!
It's times like this where I
wish I had arms to hug back.
Or at least a mouth to tell you it's okay.
But I'm really happy to
see you again, Lamas.
It's quite unusual for you to accept a
job request that doesn't pay anything,
Captain.
Come on now.
I'm always happy to lend a helping
hand, especially to those in need.
That so?
Seems to me the reason you helped out was
because you wanted to get Voxo to owe you.
Tell me, am I wrong?
I know how you think.
We still have a goal to accomplish,
and in order to do that,
we've got to be willing to use
any and all means necessary.
Voxo is absolutely vital for making
the Menagerie of Fools' Wish come true.
I'm certain of it.
Hey, Lamas, it's about time you let go.
I think you're crushing him, poor Voxo.
But if I let him go, somebody
might snatch him away again!
Hold on, heal me.
What are you doing here?
Come on now, you were so concerned
that you forgot about me?
Sometimes it's like you've
got blinders on, I swear
Hey, it's a good thing we managed
to get out of there, huh, Voxo?
Aw, man.
I wasn't trying to get
a free drink, you know.
Thank you.
I love you.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to serving you again.